http://www.citrus-gs.org/en/about-girl-scouts/join/policy.html

myAccount
ABOUTWho We AreOur HistoryOur CouncilJoinFinancial AidCOVID-19 UpdatesCareersGS System Update COOKIES+ VOLUNTEER EVENTSOUR PROGRAM SHOP OUTDOOR DONATEmyAccount
Forms
atGS
GSC Alumnae
En Español
Who We AreOur HistoryOur CouncilJoinFinancial AidCOVID-19 UpdatesCareersGS System Update
About Girl Scouts
JoinPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Welcome to the official Web site of Girl Scouts of Citrus Council.
This Web site is owned and operated by Girl Scouts of Citrus, a
501(c)(3) non-profit organization headquartered in Orlando, FL.
Girl Scouts of Citrus is committed to protecting the privacy of our
visitors. This privacy policy discloses how we collect, protect, and
use information you provide us online, as well as how we protect
children's privacy. By using the pages on this site, you are accepting
the practices described in the Privacy Policy.
If our policy practices change in the future, we will let you know
by posting the policy changes on our Web site. However, we will treat
all personal information we collect in accordance with the privacy
notice in effect at the time the information is collected.
DATA COLLECTION Girl Scouts of Citrus uses its best
efforts to respect and protect the privacy of its online visitors. At
our site, we do not collect personally identifiable information from
individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly.
This means we do not require you to register or provide information to
us in order to view our site.
Girl Scouts of Citrus only gathers personally identifiable data,
such as names, addresses, Zip/postal codes, e-mail addresses, etc.,
when voluntarily submitted by a visitor. For example, personally
identifiable information is collected in order to process online
transactions, online donations, or job applications. This information
is used solely by Girl Scouts of Citrus or other entities who are
involved in the operation of this site for internal purposes.
We do not sell information you provide to us online to third
parties. We will only share personally identifiable information with
third parties when (i) the person submitting the information
authorizes us to share it; (ii) sharing the information is a necessary
operation of the site, for instance, to process a credit card
transaction, or (iii) we are required to by law. Girl Scouts of Citrus
has no control over or responsibility for the data collection and use
practices of third parties that process online transactions.
CHILDREN'S PRIVACY The Children's Online Privacy
Protection Act (COPPA) protects the personal information of children
under the age of 13. This applies to individually identifiable
information about a child that is collected online, such as full name,
home address, e-mail address, telephone number or any other
information that would allow someone to identify or contact the child.
The Act and Rule also cover other types of information—for example,
hobbies, interests and information collected through cookies or other
types of tracking mechanisms—when they are tied to individually
identifiable information. It is important for you to understand this
law; we encourage you to read more about COPPA.
Note to Parents on Our Privacy Policy
Girl Scouts of Citrus is committed to providing a safe, secure, and
fun online experience for children who visit our site. We are
dedicated to safeguarding any personal information collected online
and to helping parents and children have positive experiences on the
Internet. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act
of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable
information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable
parental consent.
Parents can revoke their consent and ask that information about
their children be deleted from the site by contacting our offices by
phone at 407.896.4475. To do this or to review personal information
collected from children, we must verify the identity of the requesting
parent. When a parent revokes consent, we will stop collecting, using,
or disclosing information from that child. To respect the privacy of
parents, information collected and used for the sole purpose of
obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing notice is not
maintained in retrievable form by the site if parental consent is not
obtained after a reasonable time.
Girl Scouts believes it is good policy not to collect more
personally identifiable information from children under 13 than is
necessary for them to participate in our online activities. In
addition, be aware that all sites that are targeted to children under
13 are prohibited by law from collecting more information than they need.
Submissions
Girl Scouts of Citrus welcomes children to learn more about our
organization and, where appropriate, participate in polls and surveys,
as well as submit comments, artwork, writings, and other submissions
for posting on our Web site. For this reason, Girl Scouts of Citrus
follows the guidelines for interactive electronic media published by
the Children's Advertising Review Unit (CARU) of the Better Business
Bureau for pages targeted to children under 13. However, we encourage
this be done only with their parent's knowledge and supervision. We
also encourage children to use an alias (e.g., "Bookworm",
"Skater", etc.), first name, nickname, initials, or other
alternative to full names or screen names which correspond with an
e-mail address for any activities which will involve public posting.
In keeping with CARU's Principle regarding respecting and fostering
the parents' role in providing guidance for their children, we
encourage parents to check and monitor their children's use of e-mail
and other online activities regularly.
USE OF COOKIES Visitors should be aware that non-personal
information and data may be automatically collected by the Girl Scouts
of Citrus Web site through the use of "cookies."
"Cookies" are small text files a Web site can use to
recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the visitor's ongoing access to
and use of the site, and allow a site to track usage behavior and
compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements. Cookies
are not programs that come onto a visitor's system and damage files.
Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the visitor
that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If a visitor does not
want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a
simple procedure in most browsers that allows the visitor to deny or
accept the cookie feature. Girl Scouts of Citrus uses
"cookie" technology only to obtain non-personal information
from its online visitors in order to improve visitors' online
experience and facilitate their visit within our site.
LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES AND SERVICES This site may be
linked to other sites and services that are not maintained by Girl
Scouts of Citrus. These Web sites have their own privacy policies,
which you should review prior to visiting them. We have no
responsibility for linked Web sites and provide these links solely for
the convenience and information of our visitors.
OUR SECURITY SAFEGUARD The safety and security of your
online experience is of the utmost concern to us. We ensure the
appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures are in
place to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data
security, and correctly use the information we collect online.
Credit Card Safety Protecting the safety of your credit
card information is also important to us. We use Secure Sockets Layer
(SSL) technology to protect the security of your credit card
information as it is transmitted to us. SSL is the industry standard
in Internet encryption technology, which is a highly sophisticated
method of scrambling data as it travels from your computer to our Web
site servers. We also encrypt your credit card number when we store
your order and whenever we transfer that information to participating merchants.
To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit
personal financial information, look at the lower left-hand corner of
your browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending
upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security,
look at the URL or Address line of your browser. If you have accessed
a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line
should change from "http" to "https."
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to
your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished
using a shared computer.
Children If you are under 18, you need parent/guardian
permission to use a credit card to make purchases online.
HOW TO CONTACT US If you have any questions about our
Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:
Girl Scouts of Citrus Council, Inc.
341 N. Mills Ave.
